[{"answer": "Just my church and my boys. We all had to go to school and learn hand talking. I just thank the Lord they can see", "docId": "nashville.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "No, I don't", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Well, don't lose it. Last time I gave you twent", "docId": "nashville.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Well, it better not happen again", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "nashville.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "No", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Well, it's exhaustion, pure and simple, and you're going to have to take a rest or you're going to be in big trouble", "docId": "nashville.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "She's not going anywhere, my friend. This is precisely what I'm talking about. She is collapsing. She cannot go on without a rest or she will have to stop altogether for a long time", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " Who is thin", "docId": "nashville.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " I don't know who you are", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "nashville.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Oh yes, I'm my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "The architect His buildings are drippy. You know, like sand and castles. Then I got this assignment. They want to start in two weeks", "docId": "nashville.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Why", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Yes", "docId": "nashville.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "It's me. What is it", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " Bet the sheets are grey", "docId": "nashville.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " Worst time at year for dogs is when they get fungus", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " Weather's been awful. All those bombs dropping. It changes our weather. Sure not like the good old days", "docId": "nashville.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " Your hair fell out? Just like your father. Weak hair", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " Keep warm, dear. Let me hear from you", "docId": "nashville.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Bye", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I'll tell my friend, she'll be thrilled I saw you again", "docId": "nashville.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " I got them right here", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "He's a politician", "docId": "nashville.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "The Hell he did. Look, I'll see you in the morning", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "nashville.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I'm sorry but I have to go", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Everybody likes to be as good as their word", "docId": "nashville.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "His Word", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "No, you don't, so don't say you do. Bunch of damn liars. What do you get out or this", "docId": "nashville.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Your job, huh", "qsentId": 32}]